A Guide to the Episcopal Diocese of Southwestern Virginia 1905-1990
Digital Libraries and Archives, Virginia Polytechnic Institute and State University
- Women's Auxiliary--diocesan (232) 1936 (Box-folder 55-32)
- Women's Auxiliary--outside (233) 1936 (Box-folder 55-33)
- Women Workers--general (234) 1936 (Box-folder 55-34)
- Young People (235) 1936 (Box-folder 55-35)
- Young People's Conference June 15-18 1936 (Box-folder 55-36)
- Young People's Conference--Virginia Episcopal School-- Lynchburg--June 15-18 (236) 1936 (Box-folder 55-37)
- Boys' Home--Covington (304) 1936 (Box-folder 55-38)
- Diocesan Executive Board (308) 1936 (Box-folder 55-39)
- Diocesan Executive Board (308) 1936 (Box-folder 55-40)
- Letcher Gift--Richmond Securities (317) 1936 (Box-folder 55-41)
- Treasurer's Correspondence (317) 1936 (Box-folder 55-42)
- Treasurer's Reports (317) 1936 (Box-folder 55-43)
- Council--minutes and papers (319) 1936 (Box-folder 55-44)
- General Convention Matters (322) 1936 (Box-folder 55-45)
- Ministry--inquiries for positions 1936-37 (Box-folder 55-46)
- Portland Lots 1936-37 (Box-folder 55-47)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas--history (2) 1936-37 (Box-folder 55-48)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity (71) 1936-37 (Box-folder 55-49)
- Church School Lenten Offering (122) 1936-37 (Box-folder 55-50)
- Reverend Reginald F. Hall (154) 1936-37 (Box-folder 55-51)
- MacClintock, George Ronald--admitted a postulant December 22, 1936 (194A) 1936-37 (Box-folder 55-52)
- Province of Washington--general (212) 1936-37 (Box-folder 55-53)
- Stuart Hall (222) 1936-37 (Box-folder 55-54)
- Weddle Loan (317) 1936-37 (Box-folder 55-55)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas--building fund (2A) 1936-38 (Box-folder 55-56)
- Marion--Christ Church--history (51) 1936-54 (Box-folder 55-57)
- Box 56 1937
- Clergy 1937 (Box-folder 56-1)
- Council--diocesan 1937 (Box-folder 56-2)
- Ministries--inquiries for positions (B; C; D; F; H; L; M) 1937 (Box-folder 56-3)
- Ministries--inquiries for positions (B; C; E; G; K) 1937 (Box-folder 56-4)
- Pension Fund 1937 (Box-folder 56-5)
- Ridout, Reverend John 1937 (Box-folder 56-6)
- St. John's Business Women's Chapter--minutes 1937 (Box-folder 56-7)
- Abingdon--Good Shepherd (1) 1937 (Box-folder 56-8)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas (2) 1937 (Box-folder 56-9)
- Altavista--St. Peter's (5) 1937 (Box-folder 56-10)
- Amherst--Ascension (6) 1937 (Box-folder 56-11)
- Amherst--St. Paul's (7) 1936 (Box-folder 56-12)
- Appalachia--Grace (8) 1937 (Box-folder 56-13)
- Arrington--Trinity (9) 1937 (Box-folder 56-14)
- Bedford--St. John's (10) 1937 (Box-folder 56-15)
- Bedford--St. John's--history (10) 1937 (Box-folder 56-16)
- Bedford--St. Philip's (11) 1937 (Box-folder 56-17)
- Big Stone Gap--Christ (13) 1937 (Box-folder 56-18)
- Blacksburg--Christ (14) 1937 (Box-folder 56-19)
- Blacksburg--Christ (14); Bluefield--St. Mary's (15) 1937 (Box-folder 56-20)
- Boonsboro--Trinity (16) 1937 (Box-folder 56-21)
- Bristol--Emmanuel (17) 1937 (Box-folder 56-22)
- Brookneal (18); Buchanan--Grace (19) 1937 (Box-folder 56-23)
- Buchanan--Trinity (20); Buena Vista--Christ (21) 1937 (Box-folder 56-24)
- Callaway--St. Peter's (22); Christiansburg--St. Thomas (23) 1937 (Box-folder 56-25)
- Clifford--St. Mark's (24); Clifton Forge--St. Andrew's (25) 1937 (Box-folder 56-26)
- Covington--Emmanuel (27); Covington--Grace Mission (28) 1937 (Box-folder 56-27)
- Dante--St. Mark's (29) 1937 (Box-folder 56-28)
- Eagle Rock--Emmanuel (31) 1937 (Box-folder 56-29)
- Endicott--St. John's (32) 1937 (Box-folder 56-30)
- Ferrum--St. John's-in-the-mountains--history (32) 1937 (Box-folder 56-31)
- Evington--Good Shepherd (33); Fincastle--St. Mark's (34) 1937 (Box-folder 56-32)
- Folley Mills--Good Shepherd (35); Forest--Ivy Chapel (36) 1937 (Box-folder 56-33)
- Forest--St. Stephen's (37); Glasgow--St. John's (40) 1937 (Box-folder 56-34)
- Hot Springs--St. Luke's (41); Ivanhoe--St. Andrew's (42) 1937 (Box-folder 56-35)
- Lebanon--Mission (43); Lexington--R.E. Lee Memorial (44) 1937 (Box-folder 56-36)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (46); Lynchburg--Grace Memorial (47) 1937 (Box-folder 56-37)
- Lynchburg--St. John's (48); Lynchburg--St. Paul's (49) 1937 (Box-folder 56-38)
- Madison Heights--Emmanuel (50); Marion--Christ (51) 1937 (Box-folder 56-39)
- Martinsville--Christ (52); Massies Mill--Grace (53) 1937 (Box-folder 56-40)
- Merrimac Mines--"High Top" (54); Montvale--St. Mark's (55) 1937 (Box-folder 56-41)
- Nora--St. Stephen's (57); Norton--All Saints (58) 1937 (Box-folder 56-42)
- Norwood--Christ (59); Pearisburg--Christ (60) 1937 (Box-folder 56-43)
- Pedlar Mills--St. Luke's (61); Pocahontas--Christ (62) 1937 (Box-folder 56-44)
- Pulaski--Christ (64); Radford--Grace (65) 1937 (Box-folder 56-45)
- Richlands--Trinity (66) 1937 (Box-folder 56-46)
- Richlands--Trinity--Executive Board minutes (66) 1937 (Box-folder 56-47)
- Roanoke--Christ (67) 1937 (Box-folder 56-48)
- Roanoke--Christ--history and undated news clippings (67) 1937 (Box-folder 56-49)
- Roanoke--St. John's (68) 1937 (Box-folder 56-50)
- Roanoke--St. Peter's (70) 1937 (Box-folder 56-51)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity (71) 1937 (Box-folder 56-52)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity--history (71) 1937 (Box-folder 56-53)
- Box 57 1937-38
- St. Paul--Grace House (72) 1937 (Box-folder 57-1)
- Salem--Mount Gerizim (73); Salem--St. Paul's (74) 1937 (Box-folder 57-2)
- Saltville--St. Paul's (75); Schuyler--Christ (76) 1937 (Box-folder 57-3)
- Six Mile Bridge--Grace (77) 1937 (Box-folder 57-4)
- Splashdam--Mission (78) 1937 (Box-folder 57-5)
- Staunton--Emmanuel (79); Staunton--Trinity (80) 1937 (Box-folder 57-6)
- Sweet Briar (81); Tazewell--Stras Memorial Church (82) 1937 (Box-folder 57-7)
- Waynesboro--St. John's (84) 1937 (Box-folder 57-8)
- Wytheville--St. John's (85) 1937 (Box-folder 57-9)
- Bishop's Discretionary Fund (117) 1937 (Box-folder 57-10)
- Church Pension Fund (121) 1937 (Box-folder 57-11)
- Ashburn, W.E. (148) 1937 (Box-folder 57-12)
- Mason, Reverend J.P.H. (148) 1937 (Box-folder 57-13)
- Mengers, C. Randolph (148) 1937 (Box-folder 57-14)
- Educational Fund (155) 1937 (Box-folder 57-15)
- Executive Board--minutes (161A) 1937 (Box-folder 57-16)
- Executive Board--Finance Department (164) 1937 (Box-folder 57-17)
- Insurance (180) 1937 (Box-folder 57-18)
- Correspondence Between Bishop Jett and Reverend Arthur E. Koch (186AA) 1937 (Box-folder 57-19)
- Lewis, Thomas D., Jr.--admitted candidate September 8, 1937 (191A) 1937 (Box-folder 57-20)
- Derr, Morris W., Reverend (215) 1937 (Box-folder 57-21)
- Lillycrop, William A. (215) 1937 (Box-folder 57-22)
- Marshall, Myron B. (215) 1937 (Box-folder 57-23)
- McAllister, J.R. (215) 1937 (Box-folder 57-24)
- Stuart Hall (222) 1937 (Box-folder 57-25)
- Stuart Hall, Inc. (222) 1937 (Box-folder 57-26)
- Theological Seminary (224); Treasurer of Diocese (225) 1937 (Box-folder 57-27)
- Trustees of Diocese (226) 1937 (Box-folder 57-28)
- Virginia Episcopal School (229) 1937 (Box-folder 57-29)
- Boys' Home--Covington (304) 1937 (Box-folder 57-30)
- Diocesan Executive Board (308) 1937 (Box-folder 57-31)
- Diocesan Executive Board (308) 1937 (Box-folder 57-32)
- Tompkins Loan (317) 1937 (Box-folder 57-33)
- Treasurer's Reports (317) 1937 (Box-folder 57-34)
- Woodson (317) 1937 (Box-folder 57-35)
- General Convention Matters (322) 1937 (Box-folder 57-36)
- Beckwith, James D., Reverend 1937-38 (Box-folder 57-37)
- Mount, John K., Jr., Reverend 1937-38 (Box-folder 57-38)
- American Church Building Fund--committee (109) 1937-38 (Box-folder 57-39)
- Lay Employees of Diocese--retirement plans (187A) 1937-38 (Box-folder 57-40)
- Roach, Wilfred E., II--admitted a postulant April 28, 1937 (215A) 1937-38 (Box-folder 57-41)
- Clergy 1938 (Box-folder 57-42)
- Duplex Envelope Company--Richmond 1938 (Box-folder 57-43)
- Elliott Addressing Machine 1938 (Box-folder 57-44)
- Executive Board--minutes 1938 (Box-folder 57-45)
- Jackson, Roderick H., Reverend 1938 (Box-folder 57-46)
- Koch, Arthur E., Reverend--correspondence with Bishop Phillips October 10-December 31 1938 (Box-folder 57-47)
- Ministries--inquiries for positions (A; B; C; F; M; P; R; S) 1938 (Box-folder 57-48)
- Pension Fund 1938 (Box-folder 57-49)
- Retirement Plans for Lay Employees 1938 (Box-folder 57-50)
- Abingdon--Good Shepherd--"The Knobs" (1) 1938 (Box-folder 57-51)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas (2) 1938 (Box-folder 57-52)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas (2) 1938 (Box-folder 57-53)
- Altavista--St. Peter's (5); Amherst--St. Paul's--"Bear Mountain" (7) 1938 (Box-folder 57-54)
- Amherst--Ascension (6) 1938 (Box-folder 57-55)
- Arrington--Trinity (9) 1938 (Box-folder 57-56)
- Bedford--St. John's (10); Bedford--St. Phillip's (11) 1938 (Box-folder 57-57)
- Big Stone Gap--Christ (13); Blacksburg--Christ (14) 1938 (Box-folder 57-58)
- Bluefield--St. Mary's (15); Boonsboro--Trinity (16) 1938 (Box-folder 57-59)
- Bristol--Emmanuel (17) 1938 (Box-folder 57-60)
- Brookneal (18); Buchanan--Trinity (20) 1938 (Box-folder 57-61)
- Buena Vista--Christ (21); Callaway--St. Peter's (22) 1938 (Box-folder 57-62)
- Christiansburg--St. Thomas (23); Clifford--St. Mark's (24) 1938 (Box-folder 57-63)
- Clifton Forge--St. Andrew's (25); Covington--Emmanuel (27) 1938 (Box-folder 57-64)
- Covington--Grace (28); Dante--St. Mark's (29) 1938 (Box-folder 57-65)
- Endicott--St. John's (32); Evington--Good Shepherd (33) 1938 (Box-folder 57-66)
- Fincastle--St. Mark's (34); Folly Mills--Good Shepherd (35) 1938 (Box-folder 57-67)
- Forest--St. Stephens (37); Gladys--Christ (39) 1938 (Box-folder 57-68)
- Lebanon--Mission (43); Lynchburg--Grace Memorial (47) 1938 (Box-folder 57-69)
- Lynchburg--St. John's (48); Lynchburg--St. Paul's (49) 1938 (Box-folder 57-70)
- Madison Heights--Emmanuel (50); Marion--Christ Church (51) 1938 (Box-folder 57-71)
- Martinsville--Christ (52); Nora--St. Stephen's (57) 1938 (Box-folder 57-72)
- Pocahontas--Christ Church (53) 1938 (Box-folder 57-73)
- Norton--All Saints (58); Norwood--Christ (59) 1938 (Box-folder 57-74)
- Pearisburg--Christ (60); Pedlar Mills--St. Luke's (61) 1938 (Box-folder 57-75)
- Pocahontas--Christ (62); Pounding Mill--Mission (63) 1938 (Box-folder 57-76)
- Box 58 1938-39
- Pulaski--Christ (64); Radford--Grace (65) 1938 (Box-folder 58-1)
- Richlands--Trinity (66) 1938 (Box-folder 58-2)
- Roanoke--Christ (67); Roanoke--St. John's (68) 1938 (Box-folder 58-3)
- Roanoke--St. Peter's (70) 1938 (Box-folder 58-4)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity (71) 1938 (Box-folder 58-5)
- St. Paul--Grace House (72) 1938 (Box-folder 58-6)
- St. Paul--Grace House--history (72) 1938 (Box-folder 58-7)
- Saltville--St. Paul's (75); Schuyler--Christ Church--finances, reports, etc. (76A) 1938 (Box-folder 58-8)
- Splashdam--Mission (78) 1938 (Box-folder 58-9)
- Staunton--RFD #1--Trinity Church (80) 1938 (Box-folder 58-10)
- Staunton--Trinity (80); Forrest Memorial Chapel--Sweet Chalybeate Spas, Virginia (80A) 1938 (Box-folder 58-11)
- Tazewell--Stras Memorial (82); Waynesboro--St. John's (84) 1938 (Box-folder 58-12)
- B--general (88); E--general (91) 1938 (Box-folder 58-13)
- S--general (104); Bishop's Discretionary Fund (117) 1938 (Box-folder 58-14)
- Church Pension Fund (121) 1938 (Box-folder 58-15)
- Clippings (127) 1938 (Box-folder 58-16)
- Council--constitution and canons (134); Council--endowment by request (137) 1938 (Box-folder 58-17)
- James R. Davidson, Jr.--seminary student who supplied in mission field June 18-September 8 (150A) 1938 (Box-folder 58-18)
- Diocese Records (154) 1938 (Box-folder 58-19)
- Educational Fund (155) 1938 (Box-folder 58-20)
- Girls Friendly (177) 1938 (Box-folder 58-21)
- Insurance--fire (180) 1938 (Box-folder 58-22)
- Correspondence between Bishop Jett and Reverend Arthur E. Koch (186AA) 1938 (Box-folder 58-23)
- John D. Letcher (190) 1938 (Box-folder 58-24)
- Thomas D. Lewis, Jr.--admitted candidate September 8, 1937 (191A) 1938 (Box-folder 58-25)
- Motion Pictures (197) 1938 (Box-folder 58-26)
- National Council--treasurer (206) 1938 (Box-folder 58-27)
- News Notes--August 26 (208) 1938 (Box-folder 58-28)
- Reverend Henry D. Phillips, D.D. (209A) 1938 (Box-folder 58-29)
- Bishop Phillips--personal (209C) 1938 (Box-folder 58-30)
- Edward W. Mellichampe (215) 1938 (Box-folder 58-31)
- St. Paul's School--Lawrenceville (216) 1938 (Box-folder 58-32)
- Mrs. Doris Shannon (Mrs. Arthur E. Shannon)--Blacksburg, Virginia (216A); Southwestern Episcopalian (219) 1938 (Box-folder 58-33)
- Standing Committee (221) 1938 (Box-folder 58-34)
- Stuart Hall (222) 1938 (Box-folder 58-35)
- Stuart Hall, Incorporated (222) 1938 (Box-folder 58-36)
- Stuart Hall--special--The Bishop--financial records (222) 1938 (Box-folder 58-37)
- Theological Seminary (224) 1938 (Box-folder 58-38)
- Trustees of Diocese (226) 1938 (Box-folder 58-39)
- United Thank Offering--general (227A) 1938 (Box-folder 58-40)
- Virginia Episcopal School (229) 1938 (Box-folder 58-41)
- Virginia Episcopal School--bookkeeping (229) 1938 (Box-folder 58-42)
- Women Workers--general (234) 1938 (Box-folder 58-43)
- Boys Home--Covington (304) 1938 (Box-folder 58-44)
- Treasurer's general correspondence (317) 1938 (Box-folder 58-45)
- Council--minutes and papers (319) 1938 (Box-folder 58-46)
- Clergy--Reverend Edward J. Claytor 1938-39 (Box-folder 58-47)
- St. John's Business Women's Chapter--minutes 1938-39 (Box-folder 58-48)
- Lexington--R.E. Lee Memorial--also undated newsclipping regarding Lt. Col. Paul Welles, instructor at Virginia Military Institute (37) 1938-39 (Box-folder 58-49)
- Roanoke--St. John's--history (58) 1938-39 (Box-folder 58-50)
- Virginia Episcopal School--First Baptist Church (Roanoke) bonds (229B) 1938-39 (Box-folder 58-51)
- Auditor's Report 1939 (Box-folder 58-52)
- Clergy 1939 (Box-folder 58-53)
- Clergy--Reverend W. Carroll Brooke 1939 (Box-folder 58-54)
- Council--secretary's papers 1939 (Box-folder 58-55)
- Right Reverend John James Gravatt, D.D.--former Rector of Trinity Church--Staunton, Virginia 1939 (Box-folder 58-56)
- Ministries--inquiries for positions 1939 (Box-folder 58-57)
- Ministries--inquiries for positions (H; M) 1939 (Box-folder 58-58)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas (2) 1939 (Box-folder 58-59)
- Altavista--St. Peter's (5) 1939 (Box-folder 58-60)
- Amherst--Ascension (6); Amherst--St. Paul's Mission (7) 1939 (Box-folder 58-61)
- Amherst--St. Paul's Mission (7) 1939 (Box-folder 58-62)
- Appalachia--Grace (8) 1939 (Box-folder 58-63)
- Arrington--Trinity (9) 1939 (Box-folder 58-64)
- Bedford--St. John's (10); Bedford--St. Philip's (11) 1939 (Box-folder 58-65)
- Big Island--St. Thomas (12); Big Stone Gap--Christ (13) 1939 (Box-folder 58-66)
- Blacksburg--Christ (14) 1939 (Box-folder 58-67)
- Bluefield--St. Mary's (15) 1939 (Box-folder 58-68)
- Bristol--Emmanuel--includes historical information (17) 1939 (Box-folder 58-69)
- Buchanan--Trinity (20); Buena Vista--Christ Church (21) 1939 (Box-folder 58-70)
- Callaway--St. Peter's (22) 1939 (Box-folder 58-71)
- Christiansburg--St. Thomas (23); Clifton Forge--St. Andrew's (25) 1939 (Box-folder 58-72)
- Covington--Emmanuel (27) 1939 (Box-folder 58-73)
- Box 59 1939
- Covington--Grace Mission at the Boys Home (28) 1939 (Box-folder 59-1)
- Dante--St. Mark's (29) 1939 (Box-folder 59-2)
- Ferrum--St. John's-in-the-mountains (32) 1939 (Box-folder 59-3)
- Fincastle--St. Mark's (34) 1939 (Box-folder 59-4)
- Folly Mills--Good Shepherd (35) 1939 (Box-folder 59-5)
- Glasgow--St. John's (40); Hot Springs--St. Luke's (41) 1939 (Box-folder 59-6)
- Ivanhoe--St. Andrew's (42) 1939 (Box-folder 59-7)
- Lexington--R.E. Memorial (44) 1939 (Box-folder 59-8)
- Lynchburg--Good Shepherd (46) 1939 (Box-folder 59-9)
- Lynchburg--Grace Memorial (47); Lynchburg--Grace Memorial Church--contributions to its indebtedness 1939 (Box-folder 59-10)
- Lynchburg--St. John's (48) 1939 (Box-folder 59-11)
- Lynchburg--St. Paul's (49) 1939 (Box-folder 59-12)
- Marion--Christ Church (51); Martinsville--Christ (52) 1939 (Box-folder 59-13)
- Montvale--St. Mark's (55); Nora--St. Stephen's (57) 1939 (Box-folder 59-14)
- Norton--All Saint's (58) 1939 (Box-folder 59-15)
- Norwood--Christ (59); Pearisburg--Christ (60) 1939 (Box-folder 59-16)
- Pedlar Mills--St. Luke's (61); Pocahontas--Christ Church (62) 1939 (Box-folder 59-17)
- Pulaski--Christ Church (64); Radford--Grace Church (65) 1939 (Box-folder 59-18)
- Richlands--Trinity (66); Roanoke--Christ Church (67) 1939 (Box-folder 59-19)
- Roanoke--St. John's (68) 1939 (Box-folder 59-20)
- Roanoke--St. Peter's (70) 1939 (Box-folder 59-21)
- Koch, Arthur E., Reverend--correspondence with Bishop Phillips (70) 1939 (Box-folder 59-22)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity (71) 1939 (Box-folder 59-23)
- St. Paul--Grace House (72) 1939 (Box-folder 59-24)
- Salem--St. Paul's (74) 1939 (Box-folder 59-25)
- Saltville--St. Paul's (75) 1939 (Box-folder 59-26)
- Schuyler--Christ Church (76) 1939 (Box-folder 59-27)
- Splashdam--Good Shepherd (78) 1939 (Box-folder 59-28)
- Staunton--Emmanuel (79) 1939 (Box-folder 59-29)
- Staunton--Trinity (80) 1939 (Box-folder 59-30)
- Forrest Memorial Chapel--Sweet Chalybeate Springs (81A) 1939 (Box-folder 59-31)
- Tazewell--Stras Memorial (82) 1939 (Box-folder 59-32)
- Waynesboro--St. John's (84) 1939 (Box-folder 59-33)
- Wytheville--St. John's (85) 1939 (Box-folder 59-34)
- A--general (87) 1939 (Box-folder 59-35)
- B--general (88) 1939 (Box-folder 59-36)
- C--general (89) 1939 (Box-folder 59-37)
- D--general (90) 1939 (Box-folder 59-38)
- E--general (91); F--general (92) 1939 (Box-folder 59-39)
- G--general (93); H--general (94) 1939 (Box-folder 59-40)
- J--general (96); K--general (97) 1939 (Box-folder 59-41)
- M--general (99); R--general (103) 1939 (Box-folder 59-42)
- S--general (104) 1939 (Box-folder 59-43)
- W--general (107) 1939 (Box-folder 59-44)
- American Church Building Fund Committee (109) 1939 (Box-folder 59-45)
- American Church Institute for Negroes (110); Automobiles (114) 1939 (Box-folder 59-46)
- Birthday Thank Offering (116); Bishop's Discretionary Fund (117) 1939 (Box-folder 59-47)
- Boys Home--Covington (119) 1939 (Box-folder 59-48)
- Boys Home--Covington (119) 1939 (Box-folder 59-49)
- Mr. Albert Arthur Branch--confirmed April 1923--considering the ministry (119A) 1939 (Box-folder 59-50)
- Children's Home Society of Virginia (120A) 1939 (Box-folder 59-51)
- Church Pension Fund (121) 1939 (Box-folder 59-52)
- Clergy Aided by the Diocese (123A) 1939 (Box-folder 59-53)
- Clergy Conference (124) 1939 (Box-folder 59-54)
- Consents (129); Convocations (130) 1939 (Box-folder 59-55)
- Council--architecture and construction (131) 1939 (Box-folder 59-56)
- Council--church unity committee (132A) 1939 (Box-folder 59-57)
- Council--clerical support (133) 1939 (Box-folder 59-58)
- Council--constitutions and canons (134) 1939 (Box-folder 59-59)
- Council--elections and credentials (136) 1939 (Box-folder 59-60)
- Council--general (138) 1939 (Box-folder 59-61)
- Council--minutes (141) 1939 (Box-folder 59-62)
- Council--new parishes and missions (143) 1939 (Box-folder 59-63)
- Council--parochial reports (144) 1939 (Box-folder 59-64)
- Council--program (145) 1939 (Box-folder 59-65)
- Council--reports (146) 1939 (Box-folder 59-66)
- Depositions (151) 1939 (Box-folder 59-67)
- Diocesan Records (154) 1939 (Box-folder 59-68)
- Episcopal High School (156) 1939 (Box-folder 59-69)
- Episcopal Residence (157) 1939 (Box-folder 59-70)
- Box 60 1939-40
- Field Department (162) 1939 (Box-folder 60-1)
- Field Department--sundry material (162A) 1939 (Box-folder 60-2)
- Field Department--pledges and blank forms (163A) 1939 (Box-folder 60-3)
- Executive Board--Department of Finance (164) 1939 (Box-folder 60-4)
- Executive Board--Department of Publicity (165) 1939 (Box-folder 60-5)
- Executive Board--Department of Religious Education (166) 1939 (Box-folder 60-6)
- Executive Board--Department of Social Service (167) 1939 (Box-folder 60-7)
- Executive Board--general (168) 1939 (Box-folder 60-8)
- First National Exchange Bank (171) 1939 (Box-folder 60-9)
- Forward Movement (172) 1939 (Box-folder 60-10)
- General Church Deficit (173) 1939 (Box-folder 60-11)
- General Convention (174) 1939 (Box-folder 60-12)
- General Convention--House of Bishops (175) 1939 (Box-folder 60-13)
- Reverend Joseph Earl Gilbreath (175B) 1939 (Box-folder 60-14)
- Girls Friendly Society (177) 1939 (Box-folder 60-15)
- Historiographer (178A) 1939 (Box-folder 60-16)
- Dr. F.M. Horsley--Schuyler--his son Boyd at Virginia Episcopal School (178B); Industrial Work (179B) 1939 (Box-folder 60-17)
- Insurance--fire (180) 1939 (Box-folder 60-18)
- Lambeth Conference (186A) 1939 (Box-folder 60-19)
- Correspondence between Bishop Jett and Reverend Arthur E. Koch (186AA) 1939 (Box-folder 60-20)
- Lay Employees of Diocese--retirement plans (187A) 1939 (Box-folder 60-21)
- Laymen's League (189) 1939 (Box-folder 60-22)
- Laymen's League (189) 1939 (Box-folder 60-23)
- Letters Dimissory (191); Thomas D. Lewis, Jr. (191A) 1939 (Box-folder 60-24)
- Haskin V. Little (192A) 1939 (Box-folder 60-25)
- Mr. George Ronald MacClintock--admitted postulant December 22, 1936 (194A) 1939 (Box-folder 60-26)
- National Council--Department of Christian Education (197A) 1939 (Box-folder 60-27)
- National Council--Department of Foreign Missions (199) 1939 (Box-folder 60-28)
- National Council--Department of Finance (202); National Council--president (205) 1939 (Box-folder 60-29)
- National Council--treasurer (206) 1939 (Box-folder 60-30)
- National Council--Women's Auxiliary (207) 1939 (Box-folder 60-31)
- Bishop Phillips--personal (209C) 1939 (Box-folder 60-32)
- H.D. Phillips--special (209D); Province of Washington--general (212) 1939 (Box-folder 60-33)
- Province of Washington--synod (213) 1939 (Box-folder 60-34)
- Mr. Wilfred E. Roach (215A); St. Paul's School-- Lawrenceville (216) 1939 (Box-folder 60-35)
- Stuart Hall (216) 1939 (Box-folder 60-36)
- Southern Churchman (218) 1939 (Box-folder 60-37)
- Southwestern Episcopalian (219) 1939 (Box-folder 60-38)
- Standing Committee (221); Stuart Hall (222) 1939 (Box-folder 60-39)
- Theological Seminary (224) 1939 (Box-folder 60-40)
- Treasurer of Diocese (225) 1939 (Box-folder 60-41)
- Trustees of Diocese (226) 1939 (Box-folder 60-42)
- United Thank Offering (227) 1939 (Box-folder 60-43)
- Virginia Episcopal School (229) 1939 (Box-folder 60-44)
- Virginia Episcopal School--bookkeeping (229) 1939 (Box-folder 60-45)
- Mrs. Schuyler Volkman (230B) 1939 (Box-folder 60-46)
- Women's Auxiliary--diocesan (232) 1939 (Box-folder 60-47)
- Women's Auxiliary--outside (233) 1939 (Box-folder 60-48)
- Rocky Mount--Trinity--history with photographs (62) 1939-40 (Box-folder 60-49)
- Splashdam--Good Shepherd (78) 1939-40 (Box-folder 60-50)
- Staunton--Trinity--history (80) 1939-40 (Box-folder 60-51)
- Sweet Briar College--Sweet Briar, Virginia (89) 1939-40 (Box-folder 60-52)
- Episcopal High School--catalogue (156) 1939-40 (Box-folder 60-53)
- Lay Employees of Diocese--retirement plans (187A) 1939-40 (Box-folder 60-54)
- Stuart Hall--special--The Bishop--budget (222) 1939-40 (Box-folder 60-55)
- Clergy 1940 (Box-folder 60-56)
- Diocesan Council 1940 (Box-folder 60-57)
- Diocese of Southwestern Virginia--constitution and canons 1940 (Box-folder 60-58)
- Gladys--Christ (Campbell County) 1940 (Box-folder 60-59)
- Laymen's League--men of church and annual meeting 1940 (Box-folder 60-60)
- Report on the parish lines of the parishes in the Diocese of Southwestern Virginia 1940 (Box-folder 60-61)
- Box 61 1940
- Virginia Episcopal School--books 1940 (Box-folder 61-1)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas--history (2) 1940 (Box-folder 61-2)
- Abingdon--St. Thomas (2); Altavista--St. Andrew's (4); Altavista--St. Peter's (5) 1940 (Box-folder 61-3)
- Altavista--St. Peter's--photographs (4) 1940 (Box-folder 61-4)
- Amherst--Ascension (6); Amherst--St. Paul's Mission (7); Arrington--Trinity (9) 1940 (Box-folder 61-5)
- Bedford--St. John's--photographs (10) 1940 (Box-folder 61-6)
- Bedford--St. John's (10); Bedford--St. Philip's (11); Big Stone Gap--Christ (13) 1940 (Box-folder 61-7)
- Big Stone Gap--Christ--history (13) 1940 (Box-folder 61-8)